Good morning,
Mr. Sullivan.
I have a meeting
in a few minutes
with some very jittery
stockholders, Mattson.
I hope you have
good news for me.
Yes, sir. I do, sir.
Every supermarket
tabloid in the country
is running headlines about Andy
Barclay and his killer Good Guy doll.
What about his mother and the
police that were on the case?
The police were smart.
They denied everything,
which is fine because
now they can't hurt us.
But the mother's
a different matter.
She backed up her
boy's story in court,
so now she's under
psychiatric observation.
Jesus.
Where's the boy now?
Midtown Children's Crisis
Center. Foster custody is pending.
My stomach hurts, Mattson. Is
this what you call good news?
Yes... No.
I'm getting to that, sir.
Our biggest problem has
been the rumors. A lot...
Good morning,
Mr. Sullivan.
A lot of people are saying that
some joker here at the company
must have tampered with the
doll's voice cassette, you know?
"Hi. I'm Chucky.
I'm the Lakeshore Strangler.
"And now I'm gonna
kill you. " Something like...
Well, something
like that.
But the
good news, Mr. Sullivan,
is that now
we've got the doll.
We've rebuilt it
from head to toe.
A lot of it was
burned to a crisp,
but everything checks out, the
voice cassettes, the servomechanisms.
We've found
absolutely nothing.
This is
a quality control report.
I'm sure it will make
the stockholders very happy.
I want to see
the doll for myself.
Absolutely.
Gentlemen, Mr.
Sullivan's here. We ready?
Well, give us a minute. We're
not used to making them manually.
What's wrong? I don't know. It's stuck.
Just...
They'll have
this worked out.
My God!
Oh, Jesus!
Andy, you still
dreaming about Chucky?
Sometimes.
You want to talk about it? No.
Come on, Andy.
Remember what I told you?
Talking helps make
the nightmares go away.
The nightmares go away.
Well, Chucky was
trying to take over my soul.
Why?
He was this bad man who
got inside my Good Guy doll,
so he wouldn't
have to go to hell.
But then he wanted
to get inside me.
Why, Andy?
'Cause if he stayed inside the doll
too long, he'd be trapped in there.
He needed me 'cause I was the
first person he told his secret to.
What secret?
That his real name
was Charles Lee Ray.
Boy, that's a scary dream.
It was.
Dreams can't hurt you.
Dreams aren't real.
Right?
Right.
In here?
In there.
Let's hurry up.
Mattson, I don't care what
it takes. Put a lid on this.
Yes, sir. That's not a
problem. I'll take care of this.
Listen to me.
You smother this or you're out
of here in 24 hours. You got that?
Yes, sir.
Now, if you will excuse me, I've
got a meeting I've got to get to.
As far as the stockholders
and I are concerned,
this matter is finished.
Yes, sir.
What do you want me
to do with the doll?
Stick it up your ass.
Naturally, he was badly
traumatized by the murders,
but they bounce back
pretty fast at that age.
Poor kid.
What Andy needs now is a normal
family environment, a fresh start
and a chance to
forget the past.
Since you two have done
so well with so many kids,
we were hoping you might foster
him until his mother recovers.
There's always room for one more. Mmm.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Uh, well...
He seems normal enough, but
how has all this affected him?
Well, in order to
come to terms with
something he couldn't
possibly understand,
he turned it all into
a kind of fairy tale.
He insisted his doll
was responsible.
He said it was possessed by
the soul of Charles Lee Ray.
Who?
The Lakeshore Strangler.
He murdered a dozen people in this
series of ritual voodoo killings.
Are we even qualified to
take care of a boy like this?
Well, I understand
your concern, Mr. Simpson,
but I'm sure you can see that
this is just a child's way
of coping with
a difficult situation.
Andy's fine now.
He just wants to
get on with his life.
So, Andy,
what do you like to eat?
All kinds of things.
Well, what's your very favorite
food in the whole wide world?
Chocolate.
Besides chocolate.
Mmm... My mom used to fix me
eggs for breakfast. I like eggs.
You got it. We should stop at the store.
The one down here?
Yeah, the organic one.
You're in luck, Andy.
Joanne's a terrific cook.
You like sushi?
You know what I mean by...
Phil, look out!
Jesus Christ!
Look out
for the car.
Hey, wait up.
Make yourself comfortable,
Andy.
Thanks.
Well, I have to get back
to the office this afternoon.
I thought that
you'd done everything.
Ah-ah-ah...
First rule.
Don't touch the old stuff.
Sorry.
Well, that's okay.
No foul.
It's just that we
collect this junk,
and a lot of it's
kind of fragile.
You like it?
Uh-huh.
It's been in my family
for three generations.
My grandmother gave it to my
mother, and my mother gave it to me.
And who are you
gonna give it to?
Why don't you take this
upstairs and explore?
I'll be up there
in a minute.
Okay.
What do you think?
I'll get used to him.
Jesus. Did you
ever hear of knocking?
Andy, did you find...
What, are you crazy?
Give them to me.
Come on, Joanne.
Phil will shoot you
if he catches you again.
Andy, this is Kyle.
She's staying with us, too.
Charmed.
Kyle, what is this?
You've been here three weeks.
Why haven't you unpacked?
What for? I've never
spent more than a month in any home.
With that attitude,
I can see why.
Come on.
Put these things away,
and then would
you do me a favor
and help me get
dinner started?
Can't.
Got to work tonight.
Kyle, that's
the third night in a row.
I'd really like it if you'd spend
a little time with the family.
I need the money. I'm gonna
be on my own next year.
Yes, well, until then,
you're with us, okay?
Come along, Andy.
Bye.
I think you'll be
very happy here.
This is your room,
right here.
I made those curtains
just for you.
I bet blue is
your favorite color.
Take a look around.
I'll start to unpack.
Wow!
I thought you might like those.
Um... There's more in the closet.
Before dinner, we'll
go explore the backyard.
And, later,
I'll read you some stories.
Would you like that?
There are lots of kids your
age in the neighborhood, Andy.
I'm sure you're going to make
all sorts of new friends.
Hey, hey!
Andy, rule number two,
no running in the house.
It's only a doll. Andy,
are you listening to me?
Oh, Andy, I'm so sorry. I
didn't realize that was in there.
We've had so many kids here, it's
hard to keep track of everything.
I'll get rid of it.
Hi, I'm Tommy. And I'm
your friend till the end.
Why don't we get settled in, and
then we'll have some dinner, okay?
Shit.
Hello, Gabriella.
Guess who?
That's right.
The vodka? The vodka. Of
course I remembered the vodka.
Two-week anniversary. You
think I'd forget the vodka?
I know what
that does to you.
Okay, well, wait for me.
On my way. Yeah.
Shit.
I want to play
Red Light.
No, Sammy, I don't want
to play Red Light now.
I want you to go back to
bed right now.
But I'm scared.
There's nothing to be
scared of. It's just a storm.
Grace Poole.
Yes, I'm trying to
reach Andy Barclay.
Andy no longer lives here.
Who is this?
This is his Uncle Charles.
Sorry, cash only.
But that's a gold card.
That's just as good as cash.
Not here, it ain't. We
don't accept credit cards.
I don't
carry cash, okay?
Don't move!
Jesus!
God. Okay. Okay,
what do you want?
No questions. Just drive. Okay, okay.
Keep going.
Now, park
this piece of shit.
Put your arms
behind the seat.
What?
Do it!
Okay. Take it easy. Take it
easy. Please, don't shoot.
Look, I don't carry cash.
I got a gold card.
I'll give you anything you
want. Tell me what you want.
Freeze, asshole.
Take my... Take the car.
And you can drop me off, but
just, please, leave me alone.
Please.
Bang. You're dead.
No! No! No!
"The woodcutter argued
for a long time with his wife,
"but she was such a horrid,
frightening woman when she was angry,
"that in the end he
agreed to her plan.
"In the morning,
their stepmother called them.
"'I think it would be nice if we all
went into the forest today,' she said.
"Hansel and Gretel
did not reply,
"but followed their parents
into the dark forest. "
Where they all lived
happily ever after.
No, they don't.
Well, they do for now.
We'll finish it
tomorrow night.
Don't go.
What's the matter?
I miss my mother.
Oh, honey, I know you do.
Will I ever
see her again?
Of course you will.
I promise.
Don't worry. I'll stay with
you as long as you want.
My mother used to sing to me.
Will you sing to me?
Shit.
Hi. I'm Tommy.
Shut up, you idiot.
I like to be hugged. I like to
be hugged. I like to be hugged.
I like to be hugged...
Hug this.
I like to be hugged. I
like to be hugged. I like...
What was that? Nothing.
Now, go to sleep.
Nobody's going to hurt you.
Eat dirt, Tommy.
Do either of you have
anything to say about this?
I think we should
talk to a lawyer first.
Kyle, that's not funny. That
statue was very important to me.
I think one of you
owes Joanne an apology.
I'm innocent.
Andy?
I didn't do it.
All right.
You leave me no choice.
Until somebody fesses up,
you're both grounded.
But I have
a date tonight.
Sorry.
This is exactly how I wanted to
spend my day off. Thanks a lot.
But I didn't break the statue. Really.
Yeah.
Maybe it just fell?
Hey. You want to hear me
say your name backwards?
Kyle.
Hold this.
Jesus. Give me that.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
I wanted to taste it.
Get real. It tastes like shit, okay?
These things are
very bad for you.
Then why do you do it?
Because grown-ups are allowed to
do things that are bad for them.
You're not a grown-up.
You're beginning to
get on my nerves, Andy.
Now, why don't you
give me a hand over here?
Mr. Simpson is kind
of grouchy, isn't he?
He's not so bad.
I've had fosters
that would shoot you
for staring at
them cross-eyed.
Really?
Sure.
They figure you're not theirs.
You're just passing through.
The minute you screw up...
Argh!
They let you have it.
I got to tell you, I'm not
happy with this whole thing.
Having second thoughts?
Well, you have to admit, he's
a very troubled little boy,
and he obviously has not come to
terms with this whole doll thing.
Look, all I'm saying
is that he may need
more attention
than we can give him.
Phil, Andy's been
through hell.
You have to give him some
time. He'll settle down.
Besides, I like him.
I hate you.
Hi. I'm... Tommy, and I'm
your friend to the end.
Hi-de-ho.
Hi.
Kyle, do you miss
your mom and dad?
You can't miss
someone you never knew.
Where are they?
I have no idea.
My dad left
before I was born.
My mom put me up for
adoption when I was three.
Do you remember her?
I made it a point
to forget.
It's easier that way.
Hey. Break time.
Move over.
Want a push?
No, thank you.
Come on. It's fun.
Come on, Andy, please, I
just want to sit here, okay?
Too late. There you go.
Andy, come on.
Give me a break. Stop it.
No.
Andy, I'll kill you.
Come on. Let me off.
Andy.
I'll get you.
Come on, Andy, cut it out.
Dinner!
Come and get it.
Whoa!
Aah!
Mayhem.
Come on. I'll race you.
Not fair.
You got a head start.
Excuses, excuses.
Don't forget your doll.
For Kyle.
Think she'll like it?
What do I know
about teenage girls?
More than you did
three weeks ago.
I'm not so sure.
I was thinking we should
get something for Andy.
Make him feel
more settled.
Any ideas?
Yeah. How about
a Valium?
Surprise.
Did you miss me, Andy?
I sure missed you.
I told you.
We were going to be
friends to the end.
And now it's time to play.
I got a new game, sport.
It's called Hide the Soul.
And guess what? You're it.
Ade due damballa.
Give me the power, I beg...
This isn't over,
you little shit.
I'm not gonna spend the rest
of my life as a plastic freak.
Next time you're alone,
you're mine.
Oh, my God.
It's Chucky. Look out!
Shut up. You'll wake Phil and Joanne.
Kill him! Kill him!
Andy, stop it,
will you?
What the hell is this, now?
It's Chucky. I told you he'd find
me. He tried to take over my soul.
Andy, calm down.
You didn't have
to wait up.
Yeah? You know, Kyle,
I don't believe you.
You actually tied this child
up, so he wouldn't tell on you.
Is that it?
Come on, Phil.
Chucky did it.
That's enough now.
Chucky? I've had it.
But you've got
to kill him.
Andy!
Please, listen to me.
I'm not lying.
If you don't kill him,
he'll come get me.
Andy, calm down.
I'm going to
get rid of it.
There, see? He's gone.
He can't bother you anymore.
No.
I'm turning human again?
If I don't get out of this
body soon, I'm screwed.
Come on, Andy.
We're late.
Andy. Don't forget
your lunch.
Egg salad.
Mmm, yum!
Now, whatever you do,
don't act nervous, okay?
They'll smell a new kid a mile
off. Just act like you belong.
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
Is it Chucky
coming to get you?
Andy, how did you manage to tie
yourself up like that last night?
I already told you.
Get real.
You're just like everybody else.
You don't believe me either.
Kyle?
Hey, Adam. Hi.
Why'd you have to leave so early
last night? You missed all the fun.
Story of my life.
Come on now.
Where is it?
Ah-ha!
"Pinocchio jumped for joy,
shouting, 'I'm alive! I'm alive!'
"Then the talking cricket
said... " What'd he say?
"'If you're very, very good,
and promise to tell no lies,
"'then you will
become a real, live boy. '
"Boys who are bent on
following their caprices
"and will have their own way,
sooner or later repent. "
Get lost, microchip.
Am I boring you, Andy?
No, Miss...
Kettlewell.
I have precious little patience
for disruptive students.
But he just whacked...
Especially new students,
whose utmost concern
should be getting
on my good side.
I want those desks spick and
span before anyone leaves.
Andy! You think
this is funny?
I didn't do that.
Go ahead, kids. Don't forget
the spelling test tomorrow.
Not you. Come over here.
Sit down and get comfy.
You're going to be
here for a while.
But I didn't do it,
I swear.
No? Then who did?
Don't even think about it.
No toys. Head down.
Head down.
Peekaboo!
Please, let me
out of here, Andy.
It's dark in here.
I promise I won't
kill anyone else. Okay?
Now,
open the goddamn door.
Let me out,
you little dick.
Let me the fuck out.
Andy, I told you to stay in
your seat. Come out of there.
Open this door right now.
Andy,
come out this very second.
Andy! Andy!
Andy?
Andy, this isn't funny.
You've been very naughty,
Miss Kettlewell.
Andy, what's this
all about?
Chucky followed me to school. He
tried to get me again, so I ran home.
Do you know what's
he talking about?
His teacher called,
said she was keeping him
after school for detention,
said he wrote
an obscenity on his paper.
Chucky did it.
All right, Andy.
Come on.
This is going to stop,
'cause I will not allow this
foolishness in my house.
Do you understand? Open
the door. Oh, Phil...
Joanne, please.
Open the door.
Open it.
Open it!
Now, I want you to look down
there and tell me what you see.
It's Chucky, but...
His name is Tommy,
and he's been there
since last night, hasn't he?
Hasn't he?
For crying out loud, Joanne, the
child needs professional help.
Stop pretending
you're worried about Andy.
You never wanted him
here in the first place.
That's not true.
So, what are you suggesting
we do? Send him back?
You don't have to make
it sound so horrible.
Do you have any idea how
traumatic that would be?
Traum... For whom, Joanne,
for him or for you?
Look, if that kid stays here,
he's gonna tear this family apart.
Family? Is this
what you call a family?
Families don't just
give up on their children.
Joanne,
he's not our child.
It's not the end
of the world.
But they're going
to send me away.
You'll be okay.
Where will I go?
Andy.
I've lived with dozens
of different families,
and they always
seem to send me away
just when I'm
getting comfortable,
but you know what?
What?
Every time it happens,
it just makes me stronger,
because it reminds me that the
only one I can count on is myself.
Okay? And you have
to learn that now.
I know it sounds tough,
but you'll deal with it.
It doesn't matter.
Wherever I go,
Chucky will find me.
...advances over the
declines by a seven to six margin...
What's wrong?
I thought I heard
something downstairs.
It's one of
the children.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Why fight it, Andy? We're
going to be very close.
In fact, we're going to
be fucking inseparable.
What the hell's
going on down...
Andy...
Put down the knife.
But I need it for...
Just put the knife down,
and we'll talk about it.
Everything is
going to be just fine.
How's it hanging, Phil?
No. Oh, God, Phil.
I'll call an ambulance.
Phil. Phil.
Oh, God! No!
Oh, God!
Get away from me!
No, we didn't
hear anything. Nothing.
I should have
listened to him.
He'd be here now if only
I'd listened to him.
It's not your fault.
I'll take care of this.
Andy, you'll be fine now.
You come stay at the center
with us for a few days
until we can find
you a new family.
We've placed Kyle with
a number of families.
Things always seem
to work out okay.
Don't they?
Yeah.
There's your stuff.
Come on, Andy.
Let's go.
He's still in the cellar, Kyle.
Don't let him get you, too.
Andy?
We'll be out of your way
in just a minute here.
Did anyone, besides the boy,
witness the accident?
No.
Okay.
Let's go.
Joanne!
Joanne?
Bitch. You hurt me.
How much further
till we get to the kid?
A ways.
Step on it.
What's the rush?
If I don't get out of this body
soon, I'll be trapped in here.
What are you looking at?
Floor it.
Get real.
This is a station wagon.
Shit!
Pull over.
Behave yourself.
I'll kill you
if I have to.
Okay, honey,
let's see your license.
You were clocking 60 in a 45.
What's your hurry?
I have a date.
You're going to have
to do better than that.
That's one of those
Good Guys, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I love these things.
What's your name, buddy?
Chucky.
That's incredible.
I'll say.
What the hell's that?
You've seen dolls that pee?
This one bleeds.
Okay, look,
just slow it down.
And buckle up for safety.
Now, get going.
You okay, honey?
Mmm-hmm.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Come on. Step on it.
Fine. We'll just
get pulled over again.
Just shut up and drive before
I kick your fucking teeth in.
You goddamn women drivers!
Fuck.
Fucking bastard.
Shit. Andy.
Playtime's over.
Andy, what are
you doing?
Come on. We've got to
get out of the building.
Kyle, what's
going on here?
You did this, didn't you?
He did it.
Get into my office.
Is this your idea
of a joke?
Give me that.
Amazing, isn't it?
Come on!
Okay, sport, we're going to have
a little game of Chucky Says.
Chucky says,
"Move your ass. "
Snap out of it!
You act like you've never seen
a dead body before.
Andy, come on! Open it.
Andy! Open the door!
Come on!
Everybody out!
Inside. Hurry.
Stop!
Come on.
Hey, lady,
slow down, will you?
* Passin' by *
Say your prayers, Andy.
God damn it!
Pull over!
What?
Just what in the hell
do you think you're doing?
Let me go. Let me go.
What the fuck's
wrong with you?
Let go!
Crazy bitch!
We're home.
Close your eyes
and count to seven.
When you wake,
you'll be in heaven.
This is it, world.
From now on,
no more Mr. Good Guy.
Ade due damballa.
Give me the power,
I beg of you.
No!
You little shit!
Do you know
what you've done?
It's too late. I've spent
too much time in this body.
I'm fucking trapped in here.
What the hell?
Andy, run.
Andy.
Kyle.
Are you okay?
Come on.
Shit!
Andy, hurry up.
Let's go. I'll go first.
Stay right behind me.
Come on.
Andy, step on it.
Reach! Give me your hand!
Andy! Stop yourself.
Grab the side.
Andy! Hurry up!
He's right behind you.
You bastard!
Don't look back.
Come on. Hurry!
You can't get
away from me!
Give me your hand!
Reach!
I'm going to
kill you, Andy!
Come on. Go! Go! Go! Run down there.
I'm going to
get you fuckers.
God!
Oh, God!
Come on. Do it!
Come on.
Give me your hand.
Don't be afraid.
Come on.
Closer. Closer so
you can grab my hand.
Andy. Now!
Can't open it.
How will we get out?
We'll have to find another
way. Give me your hand.
I hate kids.
Terrific.
Duck!
Do it!
Andy, please.
I was only playing.
No, please!
No! No! God! No! No! No!
Holy shit.
We did it.
Let's get out of here.
Let's see. Are you okay? Yeah.
What's this?
Thanks for
coming after me.
Yeah, well, you
owe me one, squirt.
Kyle!
I've got you now, Andy,
and you know what
I'm going to do to you?
I'm going to cut off
your legs, too.
Huh?
No!
Kyle! Kyle!
Kyle, wake up!
Kyle!
Come on. Come on.
Ugh! God. What did
you do to him?
All right, Andy.
Kyle! Kyle!
Eat this,
you son of a bitch.
Come on.
Where are
we going?
Home.
Where's home?
Andy, I have no idea.